WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
SUGAR,
SPICE...
AND EVERYTHING NICE.
THESE WERE THE INGREDIENTS
CHOSEN TO CREATE THE PERFECT LITTLE GIRL.
BUT PROFESSOR UTONIUM
ACCIDENTALLY ADDED AN EXTRA INGREDIENT
TO THE CONCOCTION--
CHEMICAL X.
[EXPLOSION]
THUS THE POWERPUFF GIRLS
WERE BORN!
USING THEIR ULTRA-SUPERPOWERS,
BLOSSOM, BUBBLES, AND BUTTERCUP
HAVE DEDICATED THEIR LIVES
TO FIGHTING CRIME
AND THE FORCES OF EVIL!
NARRATOR:
THE CITY OF TOWNSVILLE--
BUT ENOUGH ABOUT THAT.
HERE AT THE POWERPUFF GIRLS'
SUBURBAN HOME
IS WHERE OUR STORY BEGINS.
[GIRL SCREAMS]
GET AWAY, GET AWAY, GET AWAY,
GET AWAY, GET AWAY, GET AWAY!
I'LL GET IT.
DID YOU GET IT?
AAAH!
UH-OH. GIRLS.
AAAH! SQUISH IT, SQUISH IT,
SQUISH IT, SQUISH IT, SQUISH IT!
BUTTERCUP, NO.
IT'S JUST A COCKROACH.
SHUT UP, BLOSSOM.
IT'S GROSS.
IT IS NOT!
IS TOO.
SQUISH IT, SQUISH IT.
YOU'VE GOT IT,
BUBBLES.
ONE SQUISHED ROACH
COMING UP.
GIRLS, NO.
EW! GROSS!
PROFESSOR,
YOU'RE TOUCHING IT.
OH. NOT GROSS, HMM?
IT'S NOT.
I JUST WOULDN'T WANT TO TOUCH IT.
YUCK.
ACTUALLY, GIRLS,
TO HIM, WELL,
YOU'RE PRETTY
GROSS YOURSELVES,
WITH YOUR BIG HEADS,
LARGE EYES,
LITTLE BODIES...
OK. OK. O.
YOU SEE,
THE BLATTODEA,
OR MORE COMMONLY KNOWN
AS THE COCKROACH,
MAY BE UGLY
AND DISGUSTING,
BUT THEY'RE ALSO
STRONG AND FOCUSED CREATURES
AND ARE
VERY IMPORTANT
TO THE BALANCE
OF NATURE.
THE COCKROACH HAS BEEN ON EARTH
FOR MORE THAN 250 MILLION YEARS,
AND IN THAT TIME, THEY'VE BEEN
SQUISHED, SQUASHED, STOMPED,
SMUSHED, SMASHED,
AND EVEN STEPPED ON.
BUT EVEN AFTER CENTURIES
OF BEING UNDERFOOT,
THE ADAPTABLE COCKROACH
WILL PROBABLY OUTLIVE US ALL,
FOR THEY ARE THE ONLY CREATURE
CAPABLE OF SURVIVING
THE EFFECTS OF RADIATION.
[DING]
SO AFTER THE WORLD
AS WE KNOW IT IS NO MORE,
THE KOOKY COCKROACH WILL
BE THERE TO START A NEW RACE--
A RACE OF BUG PEOPLE
WITH A MILLION EYES, 16 LEGS,
EXOSKELETONS,
FEELERS, AND--
PROFESSOR.
SORRY.
BUT REMEMBER, GIRLS,
IT'S NOT RIGHT
TO HARM AN INSECT
JUST BECAUSE IT'S
YUCKY ON THE OUTSIDE.
IT'S THE INSECT INSIDE
THAT'S IMPORTANT.
NOW, WHO WANTS
TO TOUCH IT?
AAH! AAH! AAH!
HA HA HA! I'LL GET A JAR.
OK, LITTLE GUY.
YOU'RE FREE TO GO.
COME ON, GIRLS.
IT'S TIME FOR BED.
NARRATOR:
ALL RIGHT, LITTLE GUY.
YOU HEARD THE PROFESSOR.
NOW SCURRY ON HOME.
HMM. SOMETHING BUGS ME
ABOUT THAT ROACH.
THE CITY OF TOWNSVILLE--
OH. I SAID THAT ALREADY. SORRY.
[ELEVATOR MUSIC PLAYING]
[ MAN, THINKING ]
STUPID PEOPLE. LOOK AT THEM.
WHAT INCOMPETENT, UNORGANIZED,
FILTHY, DIRTY CREATURES.
THEY'VE BEEN INFESTING
THIS PLANET FOR TOO LONG.
YOU HEAR ME, PEOPLE?
YOUR DAYS ARE NUMBERED!
PREPARE FOR THE COMING
OF EARTH'S TRUE MASTERS.
THE REALITY
OF YOUR EXTINCTION
IS JUST
A MATTER OF TIME!
IT'S 8:00.
[MUTTERING]
YOU LITTLE MONKEY.
[SQUEAK SQUEAK]
SKIPPY!
WHAT CAN YOU
REPORT?
[SQUEAKING]
YAHOO!
WE MUST CALL IN THE TROOPS.
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
HALT!
IN THE PAST, I FELT THE ONE THING
THAT MIGHT STAND IN THE WAY
OF OUR COMPLETE SUCCESS
IS THOSE SUPERCHARGED HEROINES,
THE POWERPUFF GIRLS.
BUT THANKS TO THE BRAVE EFFORTS
OF CADET SKIPPY,
WE ARE IN POSSESSION
OF WHAT I CONSIDER
THE MOST VITAL INFORMATION
TO THE SUCCESS OF OUR CAUSE.
IT SEEMS
THE POWERPUFF GIRLS
THINK YOU'RE ICKY,
GROSS, DISGUSTING.
THEY'RE AFRAID OF YOU.
THEY WON'T TOUCH YOU,
AND MOST IMPORTANTLY,
THEY WON'T SQUISH YOU.
AND WITH THEM DOING
NOTHING TO STOP US,
ALL WE GOT TO DO IS SCURRY IN
AND SMASH THOSE DISGUSTING BIPEDS,
AND THEN TOGETHER, YOU AND I--
ROACH COACH--
WILL RULE THE WORLD!
HA HA HA HA HA!
HA HA HA!
NARRATOR:
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL DAY IN TOWNSVILLE .
J" HMM, LOOKS GOOD,
I'D LIKE TO BUY A DOG J"
J" HMM, IT SHOULD,
IT'S MADE FROM BEEF AND HOG J"
J" SO, MY PAL,
HERE'S YOUR DOG, ENJOY J"
J" OH, I SHALL,
OH, BOY, OH, BOY, OH, BOY J"
AAH! AAH!
AAH!
NARRATOR:
GROSS, GROSS, GROSS!
GET THEM OFF.
AW, MAN, THIS IS DISGUSTING!
ALL OF TOWNSVILLE IS BEING
INFESTED WITH ROACHES!
HA HA HA!
MAYOR: AAH! AAH! OH, MY. ROACHES
ARE ENCROACHING ON MY TOWN.
WHAT TO DO? WHAT TO DO?
EXCUSE ME,
MR. MAYOR.
DON'T YOU THINK
YOU SHOULD MAKE THE CALL?
OH, YES, YES.
GOOD THINKING,
MISS SARA BELLUM .
CALL THE EXTERMINATOR.
NO, SIR.
THE OTHER CALL.
[BUZZ BUZZ]
HI.
THE POWERPUFF GIRLS?
BYE.
[BUZZ]
HI.
EMERGENCY!
BYE.
[BUZZ]
HI.
GET DOWNTOWN!
BYE.
[BUZZ]
YES, MAYOR?
WHAT? GROSS!
DO WE HAVE TO?
O.
SOMETHING'S BUGGING THE TOWN.
LET'S ROLL!
GROSS! GROSS! GROSS!
MAN, THIS IS DISGUSTING.
THESE BUGS GOT TO GO.
BUTTERCUP, NO!
STOP.
DON'T YOU REMEMBER
WHAT THE PROFESSOR TOLD US?
HE SAID,
AND I QUOTE,
"IT'S NOT RIGHT TO HARM AN INSECT
JUST BECAUSE IT'S YUCKY
ON THE OUTSIDE.
IT'S THE INSECT INSIDE THAT'S
IMPORTANT."
OH? LIKE, WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO
DO--PUT THEM IN A GIANT JAR?
[DING]
HEY!
THAT'S RIGHT,
FLY AWAY.
FLY AWAY SCARED, YOU STINKING
POWERPUFFS. HUH?
NARRATOR: A GIANT JAR?
THAT'S CRAZY.
NO!
NARRATOR: AND SO WITH HER
LIGHTNING-FAST SPEED
AND HER KNOWLEDGE OF WHERE TO GET
GIANT JARS,
BLOSSOM MAKES QUICK WORK
OF CLEANING UP THE TOWN.
AAH!
I'M BUG-FREE!
NARRATOR: THAT YOU ARE, LADY,
AND SO IS THE REST OF THE TOWN,
SO GIVE IT UP
FOR THE POWERPUFF GIRLS! YES!
NO FAIR.
HOW DARE YOU TRICK MY ARMY OF
ROACHES WITH THAT GIANT JAR?
SO YOU'RE RESPONSIBLE
FOR THIS MESS.
THAT I AM.
I AM ROACH COACH.
I AM SICK OF YOU HUMAN SCUM
INFESTING THE PLANET.
I AM HERE TO EXTERMINATE!
[BLOWING WHISTLE]
W-W-WHAT'S HAPPENING?
THAT'S IT, BOYS.
COME TO PAPA!
HA HA HA!
ALL:
UH-OH.
ALL: NOT SO FAST, ROACH COACH!
ANNOYING POWERPUFFS.
GROSS, GROSS, GROSS,
GROSS, GROSS, GROSS.
PLEASE CAN WE
SQUISH THEM NOW?
PLEASE?
NOW, BUTTERCUP, REMEMBER,
THE PROFESSOR SAID
NOT TO HARM AN INSECT
JUST BECAUSE IT'S YUCKY
ON THE OUTSIDE,
BUT...THIS ONE'S YUCKY
ON THE INSIDE!
HEY! YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED
TO HARM MY ROACHES!
UH-OH.
AAH!
CURSE YOU, POWERPUFF GIRLS!
[CRASH]
OH, NO!
I DEFINITELY KNOW
IT'S NOT OK
TO SQUISH A PERSON.
NO MATTER HOW YUCKY
THEY ARE ON THE INSIDE.
WAIT. LOOK.
WHOA.
HE'S A ROBOT.
AND LOOK. THERE'S
AN INSECT INSIDE.
I AM NOT JUST AN INSECT.
I AM ROACH COACH.
I AM THE FUTURE RULER
OF THIS PLANET,
YOU STUPID BIPED!
WHO ARE YOU CALLING
A BIPED, YOU--
BUBBLES, NO.
DON'T SQUISH HIM.
HE'S A CRIMINAL, AND EVERYTHING HAS
A PLACE IN THIS WORLD--
EVEN CRIMINALS.
WELL, GIRLS,
THANKS AGAIN FOR, UH...
SAVING THE DAY, SIR.
NO, NO, NO.
FOR SAVING
THE DAY.
NO PROBLEM, MAYOR.
IT'S ALL IN A DAY'S WORK.
IT DOESN'T BUG US.
PROFESSOR, YOU JUST SQUISHED
THAT SPIDER!
OH, I GET IT.
BETTER SAFE THAN SORRY, RIGHT?
NO.
SPIDERS JUST CREEP ME OUT.
HA HA HA! HA HA HA!
NARRATOR:
OH, PROFESSOR.
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO
WITH YOU?
HA HA HA!
SO ONCE AGAIN,
THE DAY IS SAVED,
THANKS TO
THE POWERPUFF GIRLS!
HA HA HA!
"SPIDERS JUST CREEP ME OUT,"
HE SAYS.
OH, JIMINY.
NARRATOR:
THE CITY OF TOWNSVILLE--
A SAFE HAVEN FOR ALL,
EXCEPT WHEN THE BANK
IS BEING ROBBED.
THIS IS A HOLDUP.
EVERYBODY FREEZE!
AAH!
[SCREAMING]
[BANG BANG BANG]
I SAID FREEZE.
THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
NOW LET'S SEE.
NO.
UH-UH.
WELL, HELLO.
HAND IT OVER, SWEET CHEEKS.
WHO ARE YOU CALLING
SWEET CHEEKS?
ROBBERS:
THE POWERPUFF GIRLS!
UH-OH.
NARRATOR: OH, GIRLS. NICE JOB.
IT'S THE TOWNSVILLE
JEWELRY STORE,
AND IT'S BEING ROBBED!
ROBBERS:
UH-OH.
NARRATOR:
STRIKE TWO, YOU THUGS.
HA HA HA!
HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON
AT THE MAYOR'S HOUSE?
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
TAKE ANYTHING YOU WANT.
JUST DON'T HURT MISS BELLUM.
MISS BELLUM, HUH?
WHAT DO YOU SAY I CALL YOU
SWEET CHEEKS?
OH, CALL ME ANYTHING YOU WANT,
BUT JUST ROB ME AND GO AWAY.
TAKE MY MONEY,
SOME FINE ART MAYBE, MY WIFE,
JEWELS PERHAPS,
THE KEY TO THE CITY, MY WIFE.
HEY, BOSS, WHAT'S THIS?
NO! NOT MY PRICELESS, VERY RARE,
ONE-OF-A-KIND PORCELAIN POODLE--
ANYTHING BUT MY PRICELESS, VERY RARE,
ONE-OF-A-KIND PORCELAIN POODLE.
I KIND OF LIKE IT.
YEAH, I LIKE THIS VERY MUCH.
AND WITH THIS VALUABLE
KEEPSAKE, I WILL OBTAIN POWER
OVER THE MAYOR
AND ALL OF TOWNSVILLE.
OH, ALL IS LOST.
PUT DOWN THAT PRICELESS
PORCELAIN POODLE, YOU PUNK!
P-P-POWERPUFFS?
PRECISELY.
[GASP]
OH, NO!
WELL, HELLO, BLOSSOM.
IT'S ALWAYS A PLEASURE TO HAVE YOU GIRLS
OVER TO THE HOUSE.
WE MUST DEFINITELY
DO THIS MORE OFTEN.
OH, HELLO, POODLES.
ALL:
WHEW.
WELL, GIRLS,
YOU'VE DONE IT AGAIN.
YOU SAVED ME
AND THE ENTIRE
CITY OF TOWNSVILLE.
I'M SO PROUD
OF YOU GIRLS.
AND TO SHOW YOU MY PERSONAL SIGN
OF APPRECIATION,
I WANT TO PRESENT YOU
WITH MY PRICELESS,
VERY RARE, ONE-OF-A-KIND
PORCELAIN POODLE.
OH, WHO GIVES A HOOT
ABOUT AN OLD STATUE
ANYWAY?
IT'S NOTHING.
WE LOVE YOU GIRLS.
WOMAN: AND THAT'S HOW
IT ALL WENT DOWN TODAY
WHEN THE POWERPUFF GIRLS
RESCUED THE MAYOR AND HIS ASSISTANT
FROM CERTAIN DEATH
AND PUT 3 EXTREMELY DANGEROUS
CRIMINALS BEHIND BARS.
THIS AIN'T NO FAIR, I TELL YOU.
IT JUST AIN'T NO FAIR.
THOSE POWERPUFF GIRLS
GET AWAY WITH EVERYTHING.
JUST IMAGINE WHAT
IT WOULD BE LIKE
TO BE ONE OF THOSE
POWERPUFF GIRLS.
HMM.
WEAR THOSE CUTE PONYTAILS
AND GLITTERY HAIR BANDS.
YEAH.
INDUCE PAIN AND SUFFERING
TO ALL THE PEOPLE OF TOWNSVILLE.
SPARKLY PARTY SHOES.
TAKE ALL THE MONEY
AND GOODS WE WANT
RIGHT UNDER THEIR NOSES.
FEMININE BOWS
WITH BRIGHTLY COLORED SASHES.
THAT'S IT.
WE ARE GOING TO BECOME
THE POWERPUFF GIRLS.
WE ARE GOING TO INDUCE
PAIN AND SUFFERING.
BUT MOST IMPORTANTLY,
WE ARE GOING TO BE RICH!
BOSS?
BOSS? BOSS?
YEAH?
HOW ARE WE GOING TO LOOK LIKE THEM
POWERPUFF GIRLS?
HMM. LET'S SEE.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO USE
EVERY RESOURCE
IN THIS JOINT.
GUYS, THIS IS GOING TO BE TOUGHER
THAN I THOUGHT.
[KEYS JINGLING]
[WHISTLING]
HUH? HEY, WHAT ARE YOU THREE
DOING IN THERE?
[NORMAL VOICE]
UH, WE--
[COUGH COUGH]
[HIGH VOICE]
WE WERE CHECKING OUT THE CELLS,
AND WE GOT ACCIDENTALLY
LOCKED IN.
CAN YOU LET US OUT?
WHY, SURE, I CAN.
IT WOULD BE MY PLEASURE.
UH! THANKS.
YOU GIRLS ARE GREAT.
NARRATOR: OH, NO! IMPOSTOR POWERPUFFS?
WHAT A DRAG.
GIRLS, WHERE ARE YOU?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH. IT'S NAPTIME
AT POKEY OAKS KINDERGARTEN,
AND THOUGH OUR HEROES SLUMBER,
THERE IS NO REST
FOR THE WICKED.
BOSS:
LET'S DO IT, GIRLS.
THIS IS THIS IS
A HOLDUP-- A HOLDUP--
NO, YOU IDIOTS.
LIKE THIS.
[HIGH VOICE]
OH, LA LA LA LA.
HI, EVERYBODY.
IT'S ME, BLOSSOM,
OF THE POWDERPUFF GIRLS,
AND I WAS JUST
WONDERING--HEE HEE--
CAN WE HAVE
ALL THE MONEY, PLEASE?
[ALL AGREEING]
OH, WE LOVE YOU,
POWERPUFF GIRLS.
TAKE ALL THE MONEY
YOU WANT.
[HIGH VOICE]
GEE, THANKS, EVERYBODY.
BYE-BYE! BYE!
BYE!
SO LONG, GIRLS.
OH, MISS BELLUM.
DON'T YOU JUST LOVE
THOSE POWERPUFF GIRLS?
HMM.
HERE'S THE JEWELS
YOU WANTED, GIRLS.
HA HA HA!
THANKS!
THIS IS TOO EASY.
[ALL GASP]
OH, HELLO, GIRLS.
WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
[NORMAL VOICE]
NO GOOD.
SPLENDID. WHY DON'T YOU
COME TO MY HOUSE
FOR SOME MILK
AND COOKIES?
SURE, AS LONG AS
SWEET CHEEKS IS GOING.
MAYOR: OF COURSE I WILL.
NOW COME ON.
WELCOME, WELCOME, WELCOME.
LOOK. IT'S ONE OF THEM
FANCY PICTURES.
WHY, YES, IT IS.
IT'S A CLASSIC. IT'S--
MAN: STUPID. I HATE IT.
SECOND ROBBER:
YEAH. I HATE BOATS.
YEAH. HA HA HA!
HEY, BUBBA.
I'M BUTTERCUP.
YEAH, WHATEVER.
LOOK AT THIS VASE.
I THINK
IT'S PRONOUNCED "VAHZ."
OH, YEAH?
I THINK IT'S PRONOUNCED BROKEN.
HA HA HA! HA HA HA!
OH, GIRLS.
HA HA HA!
HA HA! THAT IS SO TRUE.
SAY, SWEET CHEEKS,
WHAT'S YOUR SIGN?
STOP.
OH, GIRLS.
HERE'S YOUR MILK AND COOKIES.
[LAUGHTER]
HEY, DUDES,
LET'S DITCH THIS JOINT.
SEE YOU.
WOULDN'T WANT TO BE YOU.
OH, WHAT PRECIOUS ANGELS.
SIR, THIS MIGHT JUST BE ME,
BUT DON'T YOU THINK
THE GIRLS WERE ACTING
A LITTLE STRANGE?
HOW SO?
WELL, ROBBING THE BANK,
THE JEWELRY STORE,
YOUR HOUSE, BEATING THE LIVING
DAYLIGHTS OUT OF YOU.
NEED I GO ON?
YES. I'M NOT FOLLOWING.
THE DEEP VOICES,
THE FACIAL HAIR, THE HEIGHT,
NOT TO MENTION
THE MANLY ODOR.
AND? AND?
THOSE WERE MEN
DRESSED UP AS THE POWERPUFF GIRLS.
UNDERSTAND?
YES! THERE'S ONLY
ONE THING TO DO.
HELLO, CHIEF OF POLICE?
ARREST THE POWERPUFF GIRLS.
OH!
NARRATOR: UH-OH. THIS
ISN'T LOOKING TOO GOOD.
AND BY ADDING YOUR PENNIES
TO THIS JAR,
WE CAN FEED
THE HOMELESS,
HELP ABUSED ANIMALS
FIND GOOD HOMES,
OR ADOPT A CHILD
FROM A THIRD-WORLD COUNTRY.
MAN:
FREEZE!
POWERPUFF GIRLS,
YOU'RE UNDER ARREST.
NARRATOR:
POWERPUFFS IMPRISONED?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WHY DID THEY THROW US
IN THE SLAMMER?
SOMETHING'S
GOING ON,
AND I DON'T LIKE
THIS ONE BIT.
AND THE WORST
THING IS,
WE WON'T GET TO SAVE
THE WORLD ANYMORE.
WHY DON'T YOU SHUT UP,
CRYBABY?
NOW THAT'S NO WAY TO TALK
TO YOUR SISTER.
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT.
SHUT UP.
NO, YOU SHUT UP.
WHY DON'T YOU ALL SHUT UP?
YOU'VE GOT A VISITOR.
GIRLS:
MISS BELLUM!
BOY, ARE WE GLAD
TO SEE YOU!
AND WHATEVER IT IS,
WE DIDN'T DO IT.
I KNOW, GIRLS, BUT I'M THE ONLY ONE
THAT BELIEVES YOU.
3 EVIL MEN HAVE BEEN
DRESSING UP LIKE YOU.
THEY ROBBED A BANK,
STOLE PRECIOUS JEWELRY,
AND HARASSED THE MAYOR
IN HIS OWN HOME.
WHO COULD BE DOING THIS?
ROBBING THE BANK,
STEALING PRECIOUS JEWELRY,
HARASSING THE MAYOR
IN HIS OWN HOME.
ANYTHING ELSE,
MISS BELLUM?
MISS BELLUM:
WELL, THERE IS SOMETHING ELSE.
HE--HE CALLED ME
SWEET CHEEKS.
GIRLS:
NO!
NARRATOR:
NOT SWEET CHEEKS!
HAND IT OVER,
SWEET CHEEKS.
THAT'S IT.
I KNOW WHO THEY ARE.
THEY ARE THE ONLY 3 VILLAINS
CAPABLE OF SUCH INSENSITIVE,
DEROGATORY,
AND INSULTING LANGUAGE.
DON'T WORRY, MISS BELLUM.
WE'LL TAKE CARE OF EVERYTHING.
COME ON, GIRLS.
LET'S BUST OUT OF THIS JOINT.
WAIT! WE CAN'T
ESCAPE FROM PRISON.
THAT WOULD BE
BREAKING THE LAW.
NOT AGAIN.
REGARDLESS OF OUR DUTIES
TO SAVE THE WORLD,
WE WOULD BE FURTHER HARMING
OUR FALSELY SOILED REPUTATIONS--
HEY! WAIT FOR ME!
NARRATOR: HA HA! NOW,
THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
YOU GO, GIRLS.
BOY, I'M STARVING.
NOT SO FAST,
POWERPUFF GIRLS!
POWERPUFF GIRLS?
BRING IT ON!
HOY-YAH!
OW!
BUTTERCUP, IT'S ME.
OH. OOPS. SORRY.
OW!
BUTTERCUP, IT'S ME.
OOPS. SORRY.
OW! BOSS, IT'S ME.
WAIT A SECOND.
THIS ISN'T WORKING, GUYS.
LET'S JUST FIGHT
OUR COUNTERPARTS, OK?
ALL.
O.
READY?
0K? GO!
OH! AAH! PLEASE!
OH, I KNEW
YOU WERE INNOCENT THE WHOLE TIME.
NARRATOR:
YEAH, RIGHT.
AND THANK YOU ONCE AGAIN
FOR SAVING TOWNSVILLE.
OF COURSE, NOW YOU'LL HAVE TO
GO BACK TO JAIL
FOR BREAKING OUT
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
[ALL LAUGHING]
I'M SERIOUS.
NARRATOR: SO ONCE AGAIN,
THE DAY IS SAVED,
THANKS TO
THE POWERPUFF GIRLS!
SEE YOU
ON VISITING DAY, GIRLS.
J" BLOSSOM"
J" COMMANDER AND THE LEADER"
J" BUBBLES, SHE IS THE JOY
AND THE LAUGHTER"
J" BUTTERCUP,
SHE'S THE TOUGHEST FIGHTER"
J" POWERPUFFS
SAVE THE DAY"
J" FIGHTING CRIME"
J" TRYING TO SAVE THE WORLD"
J" HERE THEY COME,
JUST IN TIME"
J" THE POWERPUFF GIRLS"
J" FIGHTING CRIME,
TRYING TO SAVE THE WORLD"
J" HERE THEY COME,
JUST IN TIME"
J" THE POWERPUFF GIRLS"
POWERPUFF!